SOFTWARE ENGINEER · MACHINE LEARNING RESEARCHE

□ (614) 359-9199 | Sagrawalk@stanford.edu | Marww.ketan.me | Daketan0 | Setan0 | Letan0

Summary_

I'm a fourth-year coterminal student at Stanford studying Symbolic Systems with a concentration in artificial intelligence, and Computer Science with a concentration in computer systems. In my time at Stanford, I've published research in cognitive science, taught introductory computer science, and am currently researching deep learning in healthcare settings. I spend my free time drawing on my iPad, writing notes in my digital garden, and dreaming up new ways for humans and computers to interact.

Education

Stanford University Stanford, CA

B.S. IN SYMBOLIC SYSTEMS (AI), M.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE (SYSTEMS)

Sept. 2017 - Jun. 2022 (expected)

• GPA: 3.79 / 4.00

Columbus Academy Gahanna, OH

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA Aug. 2013 - Jun. 2017

• GPA: 4.52 / 4.00

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Work Experience _____

Amazon Fire TV Gahanna, OH (virtual)

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT INTERN

Jun. 2020 - Sep. 2020

- · Developed a web portal with React.js and Typescript to act as a hub for Fire TV partner communications.
- · Integrated with backend services at Amazon; deployed on an AWS stack using ECS Fargate, Amazon Cognito, and Amplify.

Stanford Partnership in AI-Assisted Care

Stanford, CA

Stanioru Partnersnip in Al-Assisteu Care

Jan. 2020 - present

- Working under Prof. Fei-Fei Li towards a solution for Al-assisted mental health assessment.
- · Developing unsupervised deep learning models in Pytorch to predict depression from patient interviews.

CS 198 Teaching Program Stanford, CA

SECTION LEADER Jan. 2019 - present

- Taught weekly discussion section and office hours for three quarters of CS 106B, over 8 months of experience
- · Worked with sectionees to create elegant, efficient solutions to data structures and recursion problems
- · Held weekly, 1-on-1 code feedback sessions with 30 students, graded over 100 assignments

Language and Cognition Lab

Stanford, CA

2020

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

NT Oct. 2018 - Jun. 2020

- · Worked under Prof. Michael Frank to analyze first-person infant headcam videos using computer vision algorithms in Python.
- Work was accepted as a talk for Conference of the Cognitive Science Society, 2020

Projects_____

Smart Glove link →

RASPBERRY PI-POWERED SMART GLOVE TO CONTROL IOT DEVICES. WON AWARD IN INTERHACKT HACKATHON.

Org-Twitter link →

EMACS PACKAGE TO TWEET SNIPPETS AND THREADS DIRECTLY FROM YOUR ORG-MODE NOTES. 2020

Autonomous RC link →

SELF-DRIVING RC CAR THAT CAN NAVIGATE NOVEL MAZES OF PAPER.

Skills

Advanced Python, PyTorch, TypeScript, React/NextJS, C/C++

Intermediate Neo4j, Lisp, Bash, Swift, Java